# ANUAR D.C DITUCALAN JR.

138 Old Cagayan Valley road, Sto. Cristo Pulilan, Bulacan. 3005 09173260429 anuarditucalan@gmail.com

To broaden my knowledge and pursue a career that utilizes my competence, attitude and experience related to computer science or in various areas for personal improvement and professional advancement.



## PERSONAL INFORMATION

Born September 7th, 1995 Citizenship: Filipino Marital status: Single

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Max's Group Inc. – Intern (Business Intelligence focusing on Database management) 7f BA Lepanto Bldg, 8747 Paseo De Roxas, Makati City **Duties & Responsibilities:** 

- Monitoring and replicating Daily Sales of Jamba Juice and KrispyKreme Using Transight
- Remoting POS System Using Logmeln
- Troubleshooting of POS System in Store
- Generating Reports Using Microsoft SQI Server

November 2015 - Febuary 2016

Cafe J coffee shop - Owner/Operator Rock Castle, Saog Marilao, Bulacan

# **Duties & Responsibilities:**

- · Utilize customer statements to analyze savings and possible value-added services.
- Promotion via social media to maximize brand identity and generate warm leads.
- Establish or identify prices of goods and services and tabulate the bills

May 2016 - Febuary 2017

Iniwow Grileed Seafood Pub - Owner/Operator Pulilan National Rd. Poblacion Pulilan, Bulacan

## **Duties & Responsibilities:**

- Self-motivated, team player with daily focus on goals
- Interact with new customers and build relationships for returning customers
- Business development
- Troubleshooting of POS System in Store
- Generating Reports Using Microsoft SQLServer

March 2017 - Present

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Hardware troubleshooting
- Programming Language (Dot Net, Basic Java, Basic Android Studio, C++)
- Web Development( HTML, CSS)
- Software Development (Microsoft Visual Studio VB.Net, Netbeans, AndroidStudio, MS SQL, MySQL)
- Microsoft Office (MS Powerpoint, MS Access, MS Word, MS Excel)
- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, After Effects, Basic DreamWeaver)

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Strong Communication
- Willing to render overtime
- Proven leadership skills and ability to motivate
- Highly Organized & efficient

#### AFFILIATIONS

2015 - 2016

**Junior Philippine Computer Society** 

Director for membership, National Board Officer Baliuag University Supreme Student Council Vice President For Media and Communication Computer Science Student Organization President, Baliuag University, Baliwag Bulacan

**Student Society on Information Technology Education** Vice President for External, Baliuag University, Baliwag bul.

**Junior Philippine Computer Society** 

Director for membership, Baliuag University, Baliwag bul.

AKAP BAYAN

Director for Media and Communication

2014 - 2015

**Computer Science Student Organization** 

Tresuser, Baliuag University

**Baliuag University Supreme Student Council** 

**EXECOM** 

MICROSOFT STUDENT JUNIOR

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### Awards:

- INFOMERCIAL FINALIST organized by the DOT Region III, Nov. 15, 2015
- INFOMERCIAL FINALIST organized by the PSITE Region III
- CHAMPION SITE HENYO COMPETITION on Baliuag University, March 11, 2014
- Recognition for being proficient in the subject C Programming, March 10,2015
- Best Thesis during the presentation of thesis for S.Y. 2015 2016, Oct. 27, 2015
- Microsoft Technology Associate (Software Developer) S Y 2014 2015
- Microsoft Technology Associate (HTML5), S.Y. 2014 2015
- Berlitz English Language Level 5, S.Y. 2014 2015

ANUAR DITUCALAN JR

2

## Leadership:

- Volunteer in the "Free Computer Literacy Training 2015"
- Active Participation during the "Baliuag University Gawad Kalinga Youth Camp"
- Active Invovlement in Community Outreach, S.Y. 2015- 2016
- Active Invovlement in Community Outreach, S.Y. 2014- 2015
- Service to the University, S.Y.2015- 2016
- Service to the Department, S.Y. 2014- 2015
- Service to the College, S.Y. 2014 2015.
- One of the Delegates in National Rizal Youth Leadership Institute
- One of the Delegates in JPCS LEADERSHIP TRANSFORMATION WORKSHOP 2014
- One of the Delegates in JPCS LEADERSHIP TRANSFORMATION WORKSHOP 2015

#### **EDUCATION**

2012 - 2016

**BALIUAG UNIVERSITY** 

baliwag, bulacan

2008 - 2012

**BALIUAG UNIVERSITY** 

baliwag, bulacan

2002 2008

JESUS IS LORD CHRISTIAN SCHOOL

baliwag, bulacan

# CHARACTER REFERENCES

Dr. Bernandino P. Malang – Dean, Bailuag University, College of IT Education 0932-858-1390

Mrs. Esperanza Balatbat, RGC – Guidance Counselor, Dr. Yanga's Colleges Inc. 0923-537-1441

Clarissa P. Vicente – Computer Science Chairman, Balluag University, College of IT Education 09157241490

ANUAR DITUCALAN JR 3